（昌文君(しょうぶんくん)）
なぜ 昌平君(しょうへいくん)の招集に応じた？
Why did you respond to Changpingjun's invitation?
（昌文君）あれほど秦国(しんこく)軍を
率いることを拒んでいたお前が―
You were so fervently against leading the Qin Army before,
どういう風の吹き回しだ？
what brought on this change of heart?
（王騎(おうき)）意外でしたか？
（昌文君）当たり前だ
Were you surprised?
Of course!
どうして戦う気になった？ 王騎
（王騎）馬陽(ばよう)ですよ
What caused you to want to fight, Wang Qi?!
It's Mayang.
そうか… そうだったな　馬陽は…
I see...
So that was why...
Mayang was...
かつて 六将の摎(きょう)とお前
そして わしの３人で―
the place where you, Great General Liao, and I
took a castle from Zhao.
趙(ちょう)より奪った城 そして…
And...
摎が倒れた地だった…
the place where Liao was defeated.
あれは悪夢だった
まさか あの摎が敗れるとは…
That was a nightmare.
To think that Liao could ever be beaten...
龐煖(ほうけん)… 何者だったのか あの男は…
Pang Nuan...
Who was that man?
No, never mind.
いや よそう　死んだ男の話など
We don't need to talk about a dead man...
But are you saying that you refuse to hand over Mayang as it is the place Liao died?
では 摎の弔いの地 馬陽は
渡せぬということか
（王騎）まあ そんなところです
Well, something like that.
昌文君 私は そろそろ
昭王(しょうおう)六将としての自分とは―
Changwenjun, I've been thinking I should perhaps soon bid farewell
to my self that was one of the Six Great Generals under King Zhao.
決別しようかと考えています
この戦いを決着として
（昌文君）決着？
In order to settle this fight.
Settle?!
ようやく
お前も前へ進む気になったのか
So you've finally decided to move forward, as well?
（王騎）そうできればと
自分に期待しているところです
If I can. It's an expectation I have for myself.
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）始皇(しこう)３年３月
秦国軍総大将の王騎が出陣した
Shi Huang Year 3, Month 3,
Supreme Commander of the State of Qin Army, Wang Qi departed.
Meanwhile, the soldiers heading to Mayang...
そのころ
馬陽に向かう歩兵たちは…
We'll now form Wu!
（千人将）
これより伍(ご)を作る！ 伍長 集まれ！
Wuchang, gather!
（尾平(びへい)）やべえ！
伍作りが始まっちまったぞ！
Aw, man!
They've already started forming Wu!
（尾到(びとう)）信(しん)が まだ来てねえのに！
（尾平）あのバカ野郎！
But Xin isn't even here yet!
That goddamn idiot!
（馬のいななき）
（信）ドウ！
Hey!
Is everybody here?!
みんな そろってっか？
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
時は紀元前 春秋戦国時代の秦国
The setting is before the common era,
in the State of Qin during the Spring and Autumn Warring States Period.
名もなき少年 信は
若き王 政(せい)と出会い―
The nameless boy Xin met with the young King Zheng,
武功を挙げて
ついに 百人隊の将にまでなった
distinguished himself in war, and finally became a Hundred-Man General.
そんな中 突然 隣国の趙が攻め入り
未曽有の危機が訪れる
Among those events, the neighboring State of Zhao suddenly invaded,
presenting an unprecedented crisis.
総大将 王騎は
いかなる戦いを仕掛けるのか
What kind of war will Supreme Commander Wang Qi wage?
そして
信は いかなる成長を遂げるのか
And what kind of growth with Xin achieve?
Presented by Anime-Destiny
Translation
kewl0210
itsumo yori hayaku kietetta hoshi zora ni
いつもより早く消えてった星空に
In a starry sky that disappeared faster than it ever has
kusanariatta deai wa
重なり合った出会いは
the many piled up meetings we've had
Editing
jagman1x3
ore wo nomikonde iku
俺を呑み込んでいく
swallow me.
kono yume wa kudakenai
この夢は砕けない
This dream cannot be broken.
Timing
G_I_A
sabitsukaseta kyoufushin
錆びつかせた恐怖心
Among this rusted fear in my heart
yuragu fuan no naka de
揺らぐ不安の中で
and the anxiety that makes me waver
Typesetting
G_I_A
ame wo saegiru shinjitsu
雨を遮る信実
is a truth that interrupts the rain.
dare ni mo ubaeyashinai
誰にも奪えやしない
No one can take it away,
Karaoke
kewl0210
FZeroWing
onaji keshiki ni hisonda puraido
同じ景色にひそんだプライド
our pride that lurks in the same landscape.
Encode
max80
itsuka kitto kanau ima mo mieru kibou fortitude
いつかきっと叶う 今も見える希望 fortitude
The fortuitous desire I have will definitely come true one day.
yowasa wo sute wa shinai
弱さを捨てはしない
We won't throw away our weaknesses,
oretachi no kienai shiin
俺達の消えないシーン
those are scenes that won't disappear.
furenzokusen no youni hashiru kibou unbreakable heart
不連続線の様に走る希望 unbreakable heart
My desire in my unbreakable heart runs like a discontinuous line.
I knew at the start that there's no end.
QC
Mistral[sA]
I've made up my mind, right now it's the time to take the first step.
Distro
kokus
Kittie
prefix-
Now's the only time.
～♪
War God Pang Nuan
（貂(てん)）でも 大丈夫なのか？
勝手に戦場を見に行ったりして
But are you sure about this? Going on our own to see the battlefield?
（蒙毅(もうき)）大丈夫
先生の許可は もらったから
It'll be fine.
I got Teacher's permission.
秦国軍総司令のお墨付きだよ
That's the authorization of the State of Qin Commander-in-Chief.
（貂）えっ？ 秦国軍総司令？
State of Qin Commander-in-Chief?!
ま… まさか 蒙毅の先生って…
A-Are you saying that your teacher is...
そう
呂不韋丞相(りょふいじょうしょう)四柱のひとり 昌平君
Yes. One of Chancellor Lü Buwei's Four Pillars,
Changpingjun.
じゃ… じゃ 政の敵側の…
Th-Then, he's on the side of Zheng's enemies...
心配しないで
Don't worry.
The relationship between the king and the chancellor is totally unrelated to me.
大王と丞相とのことは
僕には関係ないから
僕は ただ戦場を見て
その風に触れていたいだけだ
I just want to see a battlefield and feel the wind there.
（貂）な… なあ 蒙毅
勝つよな？ この戦
H-Hey, Meng Yi,
We'll win, right? This war?
戦は
始まってみなければ分からないよ
We won't know unless we actually see the war.
でも そうあってほしいと思ってる
But... I do hope we do.
（貂）信…
Xin...
最初に言っておく！
この隊は ただの百人隊じゃねえ！
I'll say this first! This unit is no ordinary Hundred-Man Unit!
特殊百人部隊だ！
It's a Special Hundred-Man Unit!
（尾平）と… 特殊百人部隊？
S-Special Hundred-Man Unit?
That's right!
（信）
そうだ！ どの大隊にも所属せず
We're not attached to any large battalion,
I heard from General Wang Qi himself that we're a special unit working directly under him!
王騎将軍直属の
特殊部隊になることを―
将軍本人から聞いてきた！
かといって
特殊部隊ってのが何なのか
Having said that, what exactly is a Special Unit, you may ask?
何をする隊なのかは
俺にも分からねえ！
What our unit will be doing, even I don't know!
But I can say this!
だが これだけは言える！
将軍が この隊を
ほかと色分けしたってことは―
The fact that the general has classified this unit differently from the others
means that we will see a more important battlefield than the others!
ほかよりも
重要な戦地に充てるってことだ！
ひょっとしたら―
We may be sent to assault someplace really huge!
とんでもねえとこに
突撃させられるかもしれねえ
えっ？ ヒイッ…
（信）だが その分…
But in return...
the distinguishment we'll receive will undoubtedly be gigantic!
挙げる武功は
間違いなくバカでけえ！
The majority of this unit is made up of the stalwarts that survived the Shegan Plain!
（信）この部隊の大半が―
あの蛇甘(だかん)平原で
生き残った猛者たちだ
俺たちが力を束ねれば
どんな敵にも立ち向かえる！
If we combine our strengths, we can stand against any enemy!
いいか？ てめえら！
Got that, guys?!
We'll crush that Zhao Army that carelessly strolled in here in an attempt to attack us
ノコノコ攻めてきやがった趙軍を
たたきつぶし…
魏(ぎ)との戦いよりも…
and get our hands
更に でっけえ武功を―
on even greater glory
つかみ取るぞー！
than in the war with Wei!
（渕(えん)）さすが 信どの
Lord Xin really is something.
最初の檄(げき)で
一気に隊の心をつかんだ
In his first speech, he immediately captured everyone's hearts!
（農兵Ａ）
すげえ… あいつ ホントに信か？
Awesome! Is that guy really Xin?!
What's going on here?!
（農兵Ｂ）
どうなってんだ？ こりゃ
信 お前…
Xin... You...
（農兵Ｃ）あのガキ
この半年で何かあったッスね
That kid, something must've happened to him in these past six months.
（沛浪(はいろう)）ああ
Yeah.
それから この隊には―
Moving on, I've been allowed to assign two vice generals to this unit!
２人の副将を置くことを
許してもらった
１人目は渕さんだ
The first is Mr. Yuan!
（渕）よろしく！
（兵士たち）はっ！
Greetings!
もう１人の副将は？
And the other vice general?!
（信）
ああ まだ来てねえみてえだがな
Yeah... It looks like he's not here yet.
（信）心配すんな！
Don't worry!
もし あいつが来なくても
この部隊は強(つえ)え！
Even if he doesn't come, this unit is strong!
Xiangyang
Wang Qi
Army
（ナレーター）
王騎軍にとって
For General Wang Qi,
咸陽(かんよう)から馬陽までは
15日の道のりである
the journey from Xiangyang to Mayang would take 15 days.
一方 信たち歩兵軍は
Meanwhile, Xin and his group marched from a location that would take 9 more days to reach Mayang.
あと９日の所まで行軍を進めていた
Xiangyang
Wang Qi
Army
Foot Soldiers
Mayang
Ow! What was that?
何だよ…
なに夜中に
ひとりでニヤけてんだ？
What're you grinning about alone in the middle of the night?
Hey, I wasn't grinning.
べ… 別に ニヤけてねえよ
ハハハハッ… とぼけるなって
Don't play dumb.
I knew you'd be excited about being a Hundred-Man General.
さすがに うれしいよな 百人将は
（信）当ったり前(めえ)だ
Of course I am.
100人を率いる隊長だもんな
Being a captain that leads a hundred people...
１年前まで里典(りてん)の下僕で
村いちばんのバカと言われたお前が
And to think, a year ago, you were Li Dian's servant and were called the stupidest guy in the village.
But now you're leading the guys from that village.
その村の連中を率いるってんだから
本当に すごいことだぞ
This really is incredible.
“バカ”は余計だ！
You didn't need that "stupid" part!
あと 村いちばんは尾平だ！
What's more, Wei Ping was the stupidest in the village!
けど 俺らも うれしいんだぞ
But, I'm happy for you, too.
そりゃそうさ　あんな田舎村の
しょうもねえ俺たちの中から―
It's true.
Somebody from our wretched lot in that country village
百人将が出たんだからな
actually became a Hundred-Man General.
兄貴なんて
隣村の連中にも威張りまくりだ
Even Big Brother was boasting like crazy to the guys in the neighboring village.
子分が百人将になったってな
"One of my followers became a Hundred-Man General".
フン… なにが子分だ あの野郎
That bastard. Who the hell's a follower?!
You've finally taken your first step to being a great general.
いよいよ 将としての第１歩だな
張り切り過ぎて
ムチャだけは勘弁しろよ
Just don't get so full you yourself, sometimes you go too far.
ああ 任せとけ
Yeah. I'll handle it.
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
しかし 馬陽に近づくにつれ―
But as they got closer to Mayang,
歩兵たちの中には
趙軍の情報が流れ始めた
information about the Zhao Army started to spread through the group of the foot soldiers.
Did you hear? About the Zhao Army?
（兵士Ａ）聞いたか？ 趙軍のこと
（兵士Ｂ）ああ
Yeah. I heard they gathered together the people from a castle they took and killed them all.
落とした城の人間集めて
皆殺しにしたらしいな
（兵士Ｃ）
老人 女から赤子に至るまで―
I heard they killed every last person, down to the elderly, the women, and the infants!
１人残らず殺されたんだとよ
They went that far...?
（兵士Ｄ）
そこまでやるのか 趙軍は…
（兵士Ａ）なあ 俺たち
そいつらと殺し合いするのか？
Hey, are we gonna be fighting those guys to the death?
マズイ…
This is bad! Lord Xin, their morale is dropping!
信どの 士気が下がっている
これでは とても戦など…
In this state, they can't win any sort of battle...
チッ… 何ビビってんだ
What're they scared of?
いいか？ お前ら
趙のヤツらは もう目の前だ！
Listen up, you guys!
We're about to face those Zhao guys!
俺たちで趙軍を蹴散らし―
We're going to scatter the Zhao Army,
and when they're surrounded and waiting for reinforcements,
包囲されて助けを待ってる馬陽を
解放してやるんだ！
we'll release Mayang from their control!
分かったか！
Got that?!
こいつら…
These guys...
うん？ 何だ？ この音は
What is this sound?
お… おい… 後ろ見ろよ
H-Hey!
L-Look behind us!
（兵士）何だ？
（兵士）どうした？
What is it? What's going on?
ンッフ～ン…
（王騎）ンフッ…
全軍…
All units...
forward!
前進！
す… すげえ…
たったひと言で これかよ
A-Awesome!
He did this with one sentence?!
さすがだぜ 王騎将軍
General Wang Qi really is great!
With the Wang Qi's at the front, the State of Qin Army's spirits are raised...
ンフッ…
but that night, disquieting information was leaked to the capital, Xiangyang.
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
王騎の出陣で 意気上がる秦国軍
だが その夜 王都 咸陽には
不穏な情報がもたらされた
State of Qin     Xiangyang
（大臣）報告！
Report!
We've finally learned who the Supreme Commander of the Zhao Army is!
ようやく趙軍の総大将が
分かりました！
（呂不韋）うん？ 誰じゃ？ 申せ
Who is it? Speak.
（大臣）はっ！ 龐煖という者です
（李斯(りし)）龐煖？
Yes, sir! Someone called Pang Nuan!
Pang Nuan...?
（昌平君）
聞いたことがない　何者だ？
I've never heard of him. Who is he?
どうした？ 昌文君
What's wrong, Changwenjun?
ほ… 龐煖だと？
P-Pang Nuan?!
Impossible... It can't be!
バカな… ありえぬ
ヤツは死んだ！
He's dead!
He was killed nine years ago by Wang Qi...
９年前 王騎に殺されたはず
Zhao Army
Supreme Commander
Pang Nuan
（龐煖）王騎…
Wang Qi...
Qiang Lei
You finish what you had to do?
（信）用事は済んだのか？
No. My enemy moved from Wei to Zhao.
（羌瘣(きょうかい)）
いや 敵は魏から趙へ移っていた
（信）んじゃ
また趙へ行くために参戦だな
So you joined the war again in order to go to Zhao, huh?
（羌瘣）そうだな
Yes, that's right.
（信）
よし！ これで俺の百人隊 完成だ！
Okay! Now my Hundred-Man Unit is complete!
Glad to have you with us, Qiang Lei.
よろしく頼むぜ 羌瘣
緑穂(りょくすい)が…
（信）うん？
Lu Sui...
（羌瘣）緑穂がいらだっている
Lu Sui is getting impatient.
（羌瘣）過酷な戦いになるぞ
This is going to be a brutal battle.
ヘヘッ… 望むところだ
You'll get just what you want.
それよか 剣を抜いたついでに
あれ見せてくれよ
Well, now that you've got your sword drawn, why don't you show me that thing?
あのトントンタ～ンとかいう あれ
俺も覚えてえし
I wanna learn that "tontontaan" thingy, too.
ハァ… 相変わらず大バカだな お前
You're as huge a fool as always.
Wh-What?!
なにぃ！
（羌瘣）蚩尤(しゆう)は
荒ぶる神を鎮める巫女(みこ)の力を―
The Chi You... turns the power of maiden mediums that appeases malevolent gods into fighting techniques.
戦いの技に変えた
陶酔の中で舞って
周囲の敵を切り裂いていく
We dance in an ecstasy and cut apart the enemies around us.
自らに神を堕(お)とす奥義だ
They are secret techniques that makes gods descend at our will.
誰にもマネできるものではない
They are not something that others can imitate.
か… 神？
G-Gods?
なんか よく分かんねえけど
お前らだけ ズルくねえか？
I don't really get it, but isn't it a little unfair only you guys can use it?
神さん味方にしてよ
Making gods your allies and stuff.
蚩尤だけではない
それに もっと恐ろしい者がいる
It's not just the Chi You.
Also... there are more fearsome ones.
荒ぶる神を堕とすのではなく
もともと体に宿す者だ
Ones that do not simply bring down the malevolent gods,
they dwell within their bodies from the start.
体に… 宿す？
Within... their bodies?
それを我々は“武神”と呼ぶ
They are the ones we call the War Gods.
武神…
War Gods?
（李斯）
龐煖が 六大将軍 摎を討っただと？
Pang Nuan killed Liao of the Six Great Generals?
（呂不韋）六将 摎は
病にふして逝(い)ったと聞いていたが
I had heard that Great General Liao perished by succumbing to illness,
違ったのか？ 昌文君
is that incorrect, Changwenjun?
病死というのは
王騎とわしで画策した作り話だ
The illness was a story Wang Qi and I created.
摎は龐煖に殺された　それが真実だ
Liao was killed by Pang Nuan.
That is the truth.
So he is quite a military commander,
（呂不韋）いかなる武将なのだ？
その龐煖なる者は
that one called Pang Nuan.
He is not a military commander.
（昌文君）武将ではない
（呂不韋）なに？
What?
あの男のことは
ほとんど分からぬが
I know very little about that man, but this much I can say for certain...
これだけは言える
He is, by no means, the sort of person to lead people like a military general!
あれは 武将のように
人を率いるたぐいの者ではない
決して
That man is a complete army himself.
あの男は完全なる“個”
いや あれは もっと…
おぞましいほどに純粋な…
No, he is more...
To a repulsive degree, he is a pure manifestation of "war" itself...!
武の結晶だ
（昌文君）９年前
Nine years ago
あの男は秦国軍10万の ど真ん中に
１人で現れた
that man appeared in the middle of a Qin Army of 100,000 soldiers,
completely alone.
（見張り）おい 止まれ！
ここは大将軍の宿営だ！
Hey, stop!
This is a Great General's camp!
そこで止まり 所属を答えよ！
Stop right there and state what group you're attached to!
全員 構え！
Everyone, take your positions!
（斬る音）
（兵士たち）ウワーッ！
では その男―
So you're saying that on his own
たったひとりで総大将を守る布陣を
突破したというのか？
that man broke through the formation protecting the Supreme Commander?
（昌平君）あってはならんことだ
軍を１人で打ち破るなど
That is impossible.
Breaking through an army alone...?
（昌文君）だが 実際に起こった
But it did indeed happen.
龐煖は１人で全てを突破し
迎え撃った摎の命を奪った
Pang Nuan broke through everything on his own,
ambushed Liao, and killed him.
…して その後 龐煖は？
So what happened to Pang Nuan after that?
（昌文君）
騒ぎに駆けつけた王騎に斬られた
He was cut down by Wang Qi, who had flew at him in a rage.
あそこまで
激情に駆られた王騎を見たのは―
That was the first and last time I saw Wang Qi so swept into a passionate fury...
あれが最初で最後だ
（呂不韋）王騎が龐煖を斬った…
Wang Qi cut down Pang Nuan...
だが 死んだと思っていた龐煖は
生きていて
But Pang Nuan, whom was thought to be dead, is alive.
かつ 今 その２人が両軍の将として
相まみえようとしている
And now those two are likely to meet each other again
as leaders of the two opposing armies.
少々できすぎだな
This is a bit more than we expected.
Most likely, Wang Qi knew about this from the beginning.
（昌文君）恐らく
王騎は初めから知っておったのだ
だから 秦国軍総大将を引き受けた
That is why he accepted to be the Supreme Commander of the State of Qin Army.
This war is a battle that was deeply ingrained in the destinies of the two of them nine years ago!
この戦いは
９年前に深く刻まれた因縁の戦いだ
Wang Qi is sure to have many comrades he lost in war...
（政）王騎には
失った戦友は数多くいるだろうが
なぜ今回だけ動いた？
but why has he only now moved?
六将同士だからか？
Because they were fellow members of the Six Great Generals?
いや 王騎にとって
摎は何か特別な存在だったのか？
No, perhaps Liao was someone special to Wang Qi...?
（昌平君）合点のいかぬ所がある
There is one point I do not understand.
You say that nine years ago, Pang Nuan attacked Liao's troops alone,
９年前 龐煖は
１人で摎の本陣を襲ったようだが
その意図は何だったのか？
but what was his goal?
No matter how powerful Pang Nuan is,
龐煖の武力が いかほどであれ
those actions seem considerably reckless for a Zhao Army strategy.
趙軍の作戦としては
随分と乱暴だと思うが
（昌文君）あれは趙軍とは無関係だ
That had nothing to do with the Zhao Army.
（李斯）
なんだと？ どういう意味だ？
What? What do you mean?
Pang Nuan did not do that as a Zhao Army soldier,
（昌文君）龐煖は趙軍の兵ではなく
ただ個人的な理由で摎を襲ったのだ
he attacked Liao for his own, personal reasons.
（昌平君）私怨ですか？
A grudge?
（昌文君）それとも少し違う
（昌平君）なぜ言い切れます？
Not exactly.
How can you say for sure?
ヤツ本人の口から聞いたからだ
Because I heard it from the man himself.
兵も軍も趙も秦も…
Soldiers, armies, Zhao, Qin,
取るに足らぬ ただの小事
they are all inconsequential, mere trifles.
あるのは 天地さえ恐るる存在が
今 この地に２人いるということ
There are only two people on this land that make even heaven and earth tremble.
Me, and one other...
我のほかに もう１人
それは
天地が砕け散ろうとも 許せぬこと
Even if it causes heaven and earth to be destroyed, I cannot allow that!
（兵士たち）ウワーッ！
I am War God Pang Nuan!
（龐煖）我 武神 龐煖なり！
出てこい 我が敵よ！
Show yourself, my enemy!
何だ？ それは　意味が分からぬ
その男 常軌を逸しておる
What does that mean? I have no idea...
That man is completely insane!
確かに まともではなかった
だが それが龐煖という男なのだ
It's true, he was abnormal.
But that's the kind of man Pang Nuan is!
うむ… なるほど 面白そうな男だ
I see. He sounds like an interesting fellow.
しかし
先ほど昌文君が申したように―
But as Changwenjun said earlier,
とても人を率いるような男では
なさそうだが
he does not seem like the kind of man that leads people.
なぜ
今更 趙軍の総大将になったのだ？
After all this time, why would he now have become the Zhao Army's Supreme Commander?
（政）王騎…
Wang Qi...
Could it be... that so he could kill Wang Qi...?
（政）
まさか 龐煖も王騎を討つために…
十分 考えられます
I think it's well worth considering.
あっ 見えた！
Hey! There it is!
野郎ども！ 馬陽だ！
Hey, guys! It's Mayang!
（兵士１）ンッ！
増援を！
兵を回してくれ！ このままでは…
Send a soldier to get reinforcements!
At this rate...
（兵士２）
おい 見ろ！ あれ！ あれは！
Hey, look!
There! That's...
Yes! Reinforcements!
（兵士１）
やった！ オオッ！ 援軍だ！
（兵士３）アア…
（蒙毅）貂 急いで！
（貂）どこなんだよ？ ここ
Diao, hurry!
Where in the world are we?!
良かった 間に合った！
Good, we made it in time!
Awesome!
すげえ！ 戦場が全部 見渡せる
I can see the whole battlefield!
（蒙毅）両軍が陣形を整え始めたぞ
The two armies have started to arrange formations!
全軍 右方前進
All units...
advance to the right.
（ドラの音）
（将軍）右方前進！
Advance right!
（壁(へき)）隙間を空けるな！
隣の伍とも密集するのだ！
Leave no openings!
Stand close by neighboring Wu!
( Flag - Zhao )
（趙荘(ちょうそう)）全軍 横陣を敷け！
All units, spread into a line formation!
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
穏やかに流れる つかの間の静寂
With the calm flowing, there is a moment of quietness...
それぞれの思いが
命と重なり 交錯する
Each one's emotions overlap with their lives, and they blend together.
王騎 そして龐煖
Wang Qi and Pang Nuan.
９年の時を経て 再び対峙(たいじ)した両者
After nine years of time, these two have confronted each other once again.
その胸に秘めたものは―
Is what dwells in their hearts hatred? Ambition? Or perhaps...
憎しみか 野望か　それとも…
The fated battle now begins.
運命の戦いが今 始まる！
michi wa tsuzuku yume wo oimotome
路は続く　夢を追い求め
The path goes on, chasing after a dream.
nozomu saki ni kimi no ashita wa aru no?
望む先に　君の明日はあるの？
Will your tomorrow be at the place my hopes lead?
kizutsuite kokoro mo mada kawaku nara
傷ついて　心もまだ渇くなら
If I get hurt and my heart is still thirsty,
koko e kite nando demo utau kara
ここへ来て何度でも歌うから
I'll come here and sing as many times as it takes.
owari naki tatakai no naka de
終わりなき戦いの中で
In this endless battle
kimi wa tsuyoku kawaru
君は強く変わる
You change to become stronger.
kono sora wo kirisaita ikazuchi wa kimi
この空を切り裂いた　雷は君
The lightning that cut apart this sky is you.
osore wo koete tachimukau hikari no ya hashiridasu
恐れを超えて立ち向かう　光の矢　走りだす
The arrow of light that overcomes fear faces forward and shoots forth.
tsukamu sadame shinjitsuzukeru no...
掴む　運命　信じ続けるの…
I'll grab onto the destiny I've always believed in...
～♪
Preview
（信）その任務
この百人隊が引き受けた！
This Hundred-Man Unit accepts its mission!
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
迷わず ただまっすぐに突き進む
Without hesitation, they merely plunge forward.
それが こいつらの強さ！
That is their strength!
Birth of the
Feixin Unit
End
次回 “飛信(ひしん)隊 誕生”
Next time,